New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 1/16/91-4/6/92. (Box 36)
  - Cornell Univ. Land Grant & Statutory College Affairs Comm A126 Harkness Building, Medical College, NY, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Jan 23, 4:30pm
  - UUP Legislative Breakfast Albany Room, Empire State Plaza, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Jan 28, 8 am
  - Annual Lincoln Dinner, NYC CLC Waldorf, Badildon Room Room- Sheraton Centre, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Meeting w/Jerry Rodgers, National Park Service, Dept. of the interior, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Feb 5, 9:30am
  - US Dept. of Interior, Labor History Sub-Comm. Meeting, Rm. 3004 Main Interior building 1849 C Street, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Feb 5, 4pm
  - Education committee of SCANS, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Feb 6, 2pm
  - US Dept. of Education, AFT Building, Washington, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    feb 6, 9am
  - National Park Service Advisory Panel Meeting, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Feb 6
  - Human Resource Develop. Inst. Meeting, 815 16th Street, NW Room 405, Washington DC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Feb 6, 10am
  - NYSUT Board of Directors Holiday Inn, LaGuardia Airport, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Feb 7-8
  - JTPA Retraining & Union Involvement Subcommittee, UFT, 3rd Floor New York City (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - AFT Futures Committee Meeting Washington Hilton & Towers 1919 Connecticut Avenue, NW, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Feb 11, 9:30am
  - AFT Executive Council Washington DC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    Feb 12-13
  - Council on Health Care Financing 150 State Street, Albany, NY, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    Feb 13, 1pm
  - AFL-CIO Winter Meetings Sheraton Bal Harbour, FL, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - NYSCOVE Meeting with Board of Regents, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Meeting w/ D. Gillette & W. Vog Here, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Feb 21, 10am
  - Labor Legacy Meeting, NYS AFL-CIO 100 S. Swan Street, Albany, NY, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    Feb 21, 3:30pm
  - National Park System Adv. Bd. Holiday Inn Crowne Pl., NO, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Career Pathways Task Force Educ. Bldg., Meeting Rooms A&B 5th Floor, 89 Washington Avenue, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Feb 24, 10:45am
  - united Way of New York State, Board of directors Meeting (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - United Way of NYS, 155 Washington Ave, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University Bd. Of Trustees Herber F. Johnson Museum of Art Trustee Meeting Room, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    Mar 6-7, 9am
  - Meeting with Lorraine Merrick and Wally Vog SED, EBA 979, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Mar 9, 12pm
  - AFT Local President's Conference Hyatt Regency Capitol Hill, Washington DC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    Mar 13,15
  - Labor Legacy Group w/Eastern European Delegation, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Mar 18, 1:30pm
  - NYSUT RA NY Hilton Hotel, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    Mar 19-21
  - Staff Meeting, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    Mar 23, 11am
  - Council on Health Care Financing 150 State Street, Albany, NY, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    Mar 24, 1pm
  - 1992 congressional Breakfast NYS AFL-CIO, H137 Capitol Room - embassy Row (Box 36, Folder 34)
    Mar 25, 8am
  - 5th Annual NYS Assembly Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force Legisl. Conference Labor Luncheon, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Mar 30
  - ITEA Conference, Hyatt Regency Hotel, Nocollet Avenue, Minneapolis, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    Mar 26, 2:30-3:45pm
  - Cnl. Of Chief State School Officer New Career Paths through Youth Apprenticeship Council's Office 1 Massachusetts Avenue, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    Mar 27
  - Jury Service, Federal Court US Post Office, 445 Broadway, room 442, Albany, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - New Career Paths Through Youth Apprenticeship - CCSSO Selection Panel, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - NYSCOVE, Room 979, EBA 89 Washington Ave, Albany, NY, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    April 2, 10am
  - Hofstra University School of Law Reception, Senate 4th Fl., Foyer, Capitol, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    April 6, 5:30am
- Child Labor Files, n.d.. (Box 37)
  - Child Labor (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Child Labor (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Child Labor - New York State Department of Labor - Public Hearing in the Matter of Child Labor Law Review, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Aug 10, 10am
  - Child Labor - Transcript Proceedings of the Child Labor Law Review, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Aug 3, 10:15am
  - Child Labor - Public Hearing: child Labor Law Review, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Jul 20
  - Child Labor - Public Hearing on Child Labor, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Jul. 27
  - Child Labor - Child Labor Law Review, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Jul 12
  - Child Labor - Cleary Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Child Labor - Cole Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Child Labor - History School Curriculum (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - child Labor - Background Info (Box 37, Folder 11)
    1 of 4
  - Child Labor - Background Info (Box 37, Folder 12)
    2 of 4
  - child Labor - Background Info (Box 37, Folder 13)
    3 of 4
  - Child Labor Background Info (Box 37, Folder 14)
    4 of 4
- Lewiston, Niagara County, NY Political Campaigns, 1970s to 1980s. (Box 38)
  - Lewiston, Niagara County, NY - Political Campaigns, 1970-1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Lewiston, Niagara County, NY - Political Campaigns, 1970-1990 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Lewiston, Niagara County, NY - Political Campaigns, 1970-1990 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Slideshows, n.d.. (Box 39)
  - The New Workplace (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - SCANS (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Southtown Teachers Center, Curriculum Frameworks, Cheek towaga Central HS Auditorium 3600 Union road, Cheektowaga, NY, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    june 1
  - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards - Make a Promise (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Corning Slides - The New American Worker (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Human Resources Development Institute (HROI), 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - New York State Coalition for compact collaboration - Improving Our Schools, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Aug.
  - A New Compact for Learning (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - A New Compact for Learning (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - National Skill Standards Board (NSSB) (Box 39, Folder 10)